Dwight D. Gunning

dwight@dwightgunning.com | http://www.dwightgunning.com +31 6 23 63 83 44

Summary

Dwight is a technology and product-oriented entrepreneur. He brings 12 years experience managing successful teams, designing and implementing web and mobile applications, and architecting complex distributed systems.

In recent years Dwight has co-founded two bootstrapped startups and was an early hire for a VC-funded growth startup. He regularly gives public talks about entrepreneurship, technology and innovation. Prior to his startups, Dwight was a successful technology consultant who managed teams delivering IT solutions for Fortune 500 and Government clients.

His broad project experience makes him well placed to build technical teams and lead product development, while still getting hands-on with the full-stack.

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/dwightgunning

Angel.co <u>https://angel.co/dwightgunning</u>

Experience

Lead Software Engineer @ The Cloakroom B.V.

October 2014 - July 2015

The Cloakroom, founded in 2014 and having raised >€1.1M, is an online personal shopping service for men. As the third technical hire I led several website design initiatives, led the expansion of the online customer portal, and performed conversion rate optimisation. In addition to customer facing systems, I also was involved in the design and implementation of several mission critical back-office systems relating to payments and fulfilment.

Co-Founder @ Epic Labs B.V.

September 2013 - October 2014

Epic Labs was incorporated by three entrepreneurs to rapidly execute the Lean Startup method with the aim of transitioning into a high-growth business. I led product for three beta products including Butler (On-demand recipe and ingredient delivery), Beagle (Meta-search for online courses) and Knownly (a website hosting platform with zero servers for freelancers and SMBs).

Founder @ Revirda, Inc.

January 2012 - September 2013

Revirda was a mobile app providing taxi drivers with real-time forecasts for passenger demand. As initial founder, I recruited two additional cofounders and developed the initial beta product who were acquired via industry channels as well as mainstream press coverage. Due to financial constraints and limited traction, the business was ultimately wound down.

Manager @ Accenture

Jan 2005 - December 2013 (Australia & The Netherlands)

While working at Accenture I performed a diverse range of Project Management roles. A major highlight was my role as a manager leading a distributed team of ten developers to deliver a trading platform to the Capital Markets division of a major Dutch bank. Additionally as an expert in website performance, I developed operational procedures and training programs for a major Dutch oil and gas company with workers based in four continents.

Education

Bachelor of Information Technology @ Queensland University of Technology

- *Major:* Software Engineering
- Grade Point Average: 5.5 (scale 3 through to 7)

Personal Highlights

- 2016: Visiting Entrepreneur to Brisbane City Council and QLD State Government
- 2010-15: Facilitated 22nd Startup Weekend; Europe, Asia and the US.
- 2015: Summited Mt Kilimanjaro (4,877m); the highest mountain in Africa.
- 2011: Graduated from the Founder Institute; early-stage entrepreneur academy
- 2008: Completed the Gold Coast Marathon

References

Available on request.